{"data":[{"question":"An uncultivated tea plant might grow about 30 feet height.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"uncultivated","b":"tea plant","c":"about","d":"height","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Height-> high","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"A galaxy, where may include billions of stars, is held together by gravitational attraction.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"where","b":"of","c":"is","d":"by","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Where-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Rocks can be broken apart by water that seeps into the cracks and freeze in low temperatures.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"broken apart","b":"that","c":"freeze","d":"temperatures","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Freeze-> freezes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Alexander Graham Bell was once a teacher who run a school for the deaf in Massachusetts.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"once","b":"run","c":"for","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Run-> ran","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Some fish use their sense of smell as a guide when return to a spawning site.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"fish","b":"their","c":"as","d":"return","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Return-> returning","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"In Quebec, Canada, the flowing of the maple sap is one of the first sign of spring.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"the flowing","c":"is","d":"sign","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Sign-> signs","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Antique auctions are getting more and more popular in the United States because increasing public awareness of the value of investing in antiques.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"auctions","b":"more and more","c":"because","d":"the value of","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Because-> because of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Archaeological evidence reveals that Native Americans lived on the East Coast of the United States 13 centuries before.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"reveals that","b":"lived on","c":"of the","d":"before","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Before-> ago","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Diamond itself is the only material hard enough to cut and polishes diamonds.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"itself","b":"only","c":"hard enough","d":"polishes","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Polishes-> polish","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The change from day to night results the rotation of the Earth.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"change","b":"to","c":"results","d":"the Earth","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Results-> results from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"}]}